[
    {
        "question": "a",
        "ans": "あ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "i",
        "ans": "い",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "u",
        "ans": "う",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "e",
        "ans": "え",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "o",
        "ans": "お",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ka",
        "ans": "か",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ki",
        "ans": "き",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ku",
        "ans": "く",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ke",
        "ans": "け",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ko",
        "ans": "こ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "sa",
        "ans": "さ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "shi",
        "ans": "し",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "su",
        "ans": "す",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "se",
        "ans": "せ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "so",
        "ans": "そ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ta",
        "ans": "な",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "Chi",
        "ans": "チ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "tu",
        "ans": "ツ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "te",
        "ans": "テ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "to",
        "ans": "ト",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "na",
        "ans": "な",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ni",
        "ans": "に",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "nu",
        "ans": "ぬ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ne",
        "ans": "ね",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "no",
        "ans": "の",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ha",
        "ans": "は",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "hi",
        "ans": "ひ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "fu",
        "ans": "ふ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "he",
        "ans": "ヘ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ho",
        "ans": "ほ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ma",
        "ans": "ま",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "mi",
        "ans": "み",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "mu",
        "ans": "む",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "me",
        "ans": "め",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "mo",
        "ans": "も",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ya",
        "ans": "や",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "yu",
        "ans": "ゆ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "yo",
        "ans": "よ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ra",
        "ans": "ら",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ri",
        "ans": "り",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ru",
        "ans": "る",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "re",
        "ans": "れ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ro",
        "ans": "ろ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "wa",
        "ans": "わ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "wo",
        "ans": "を",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ga",
        "ans": "が",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "gi",
        "ans": "ぎ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "gu",
        "ans": "ぐ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ge",
        "ans": "げ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "go",
        "ans": "ご",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "za",
        "ans": "ざ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "Ji",
        "ans": "じ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "zu",
        "ans": "ず",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ze",
        "ans": "ぜ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "zo",
        "ans": "ぞ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "da",
        "ans": "だ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "Ji",
        "ans": "ぢ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "zu",
        "ans": "づ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "de",
        "ans": "で",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "do",
        "ans": "ど",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "ba",
        "ans": "ば",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "bi",
        "ans": "び",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "bu",
        "ans": "ぶ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "be",
        "ans": "べ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "bo",
        "ans": "ぼ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "pa",
        "ans": "ぱ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "pi",
        "ans": "ぱ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "pu",
        "ans": "ぷ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "pe",
        "ans": "ぺ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "po",
        "ans": "ぽ",
        "themeId":2
    },
    {
        "question": "n",
        "ans": "ん",
        "themeId":2
    }
]